Hello everyone! This is Hitomi Takamatsu from Equal Love!
Yes, that's right, the Equal Love Boat Racing Club has come to Mimako, a boat racing club located in Shiga Prefecture, Japan!
Wow! We finally made it to Shiga Prefecture!
We are here again, this time as an official business!
Thank you very much!
So, soooooooooooo! A boy from Ikolab boat racing club came to see us!
Come in!
Hi!
Please come on in!
Yay!
Finally, Mayuka came!
I wish I could have come!
Thank you!
Finally!
I've been waiting for you!
Thank you!
I've actually played Mayuka before, haven't I?
Yeah, I've done it online.
Is it great?
I won a trifecta.
Oh, my God!
Only Mayuka and I are registered.
You won!
You did!
But that was like a year ago.
That long ago?
I wonder if we're back to where we were a year ago.
Well, I'll take beginner's luck again today.
Let's go!
I'm going to win!
I'm off!
So, here we are at the 4th floor restaurant
Boat Queen Restaurant on the 4th floor!
Yay!
This restaurant is a great place to eat and watch the race
and you can also see the stores.
I can see the stores
You can see the stores and the stores and the stores and the stores
You can see the stores
You can watch the stores
I can see the stores, I can see the stores, I can see the stores, I can see the stores
You can see the stores
You can also see the race
It's amazing
Right in front of you
It's so spread out!
It's rare to find a restaurant with such a panoramic view
It's rare to find a restaurant with such a panoramic view.
I see.
I'm so excited!
I'm sure it'll be delicious.
I'm hungry.
I'm starving.
So you're going to eat now?
There's so much to choose from.
I feel like I've been burned by the sun.
I know.
Tanned menu.
I like it.
Nice.
The famous Bira-chan Curry
I'd like to have the famous Bira-chan Curry today!
Yes, Bira-chan Curry.
This is amazing!
It looks so filling!
It's cheap!
Cheap!
Cheap because I want to get warm.
That's right.
Let's have the Kitsune Udon!
I'd like to have the Kitsune Udon and Bira-chan Curry.
Yes, please.
Now that your order has been placed, today's Boat Race Biwako.
I'll tell you the trend, Micah. There are 24 boat race tracks in Japan.
Lake Biwa here is the southern water surface of a city in the whole country. What? It's difficult. Doesn't it look difficult already?
I don't know. It always feels like it's rippling. That's true.
It's high in elevation, so it's prone to waves, and the surface conditions change a lot depending on the season and the day.
It's difficult because the water is hard with coal water. What do you mean? What do you mean, hard water?
What do you mean, "hard"? I don't know. It's very hard here.
It's only possible at right angles. It might be easier at right angles, but I'm sure I'm wrong.
So we can expect a bumpy race. We can go for the hole.
My car is white on the member side, and it's my birthday, January 21st, so...
One and two, why not? But it's ticking on. I'm expecting a bit of a hole today. What do you say?
How do you want to go today? I'm not really into 1.
I don't have any feelings for number 2 either. I've got a good feeling about it.
There are many colors, but the first one is white. White is definitely more important to me than the first one.
Not because it's 1, but because it's white.
In the last 3 months, the first place rate of course 1 is 58.1, which is more than half, and it's not so different from the National Weaponry.
Also, boat racers belong to different branches, and this Shiga branch has some really famous racers.
Who is it?
First of all, two very famous athletes, Baba Josiah and Emi Endo.
Baba is ranked 3rd in the money list for 2023. Isn't that amazing?
In 2012, she set the Japanese record for the fastest 3-week 1800m race and won the fastest race of her career.
He's a great athlete, a very fast one. Everyone knows that.
In December of 2023, he'll earn his 24th New Boat Racing Association President's Medal, making him only the 11th person in history to qualify for the Golden Racer Award.
Isn't that amazing? It's amazing. Are you going to be there today?
I don't know if she's on vacation somewhere today.
The other woman, Emi Endo... is so in love with me, the director, that she says she'll be a racer forever.
I really love her! I was in middle school, right? I used to cheer for her at Momocha Cha Cha.
There is the highest grade SG race called Boat Race Classic held in March 2022.
In March 2022, there is the Boat Race Classic, the highest grade SG race, and she was the only woman to win the first place in the race, which is open to both men and women.
It's amazing. Men win most of the races.
But Emi Endo won as a woman.
That's amazing! That's huge! She's not here today.
But Emi Endo will be competing in the Ladies' All-Star Race at the Boat Race Diaco from February 20th to February 25th.
I'm going to support her very much!
So it was a little bit later. This is the time of the photo shoot.
It was a little bit later. I'm super excited.
The service is starting. It's starting now? It's started.
This shows that 4 is late, so 3 is coming. 1,3,4.
It's a little harder than I thought. So I think we should go with white.
We're done. One, three, four.
Your drinks have arrived. Thank you.
Nami-Nami Cola.
Oh, my God! Just in time. Beautiful crystal.
Bon appétit. Bon appétit.
Bon appétit!
The cola stings.
It just keeps coming out!
Start of the next 4 races
Exhibit.
Can you show us one? For us.
That's what the conditions are like today.
It's nice of them to show us.
I've seen it before, when they decide by name.
Does the director decide on the face?
Yes, he does.
I can tell when a director decides on a face.
The directors choose us based on our faces.
They know us.
They auditioned us.
You're right.
That's what I'm talking about.
Here's your lunch.
Thank you very much.
It'll warm you up.
Looks delicious!
Ta-da!
Hikitsune udon
Smells so good!
Delicious for sure!
Looks delicious!
And Mito!
There are so many of them!
It's dangerous.
It's big.
Peachan curry...
Amazing.
Seven
Seven fried shrimp.
That's like 880 yen.
Isn't that cheap?
It's so huge!
How can you tell how big it is?
It's huge!
How's it look?
It's so big!
It's amazing!
Shall we eat?
Let's eat.
Bon appétit!
Why are there seven of these?
It's called Mina-chan.
Mina-chan.
Mina means...
Tail
and Bee is called
Bee
Bee.
I see.
That's why there are seven.
That's gorgeous!
That's too cheap.
Too cheap.
Bon appétit!
I love eating curry at the boat race track!
It warms you up!
Delicious!
Yeah, I'm interested.
Mmm!
Hot!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
It's so hot!
Oh, my.
We each have our own, right? The famous
Yes, they do.
Like food.
So, Prayoko...
Mina-chan.
Mina-chan Curry.
Please try it, everyone!
Mmmm...
Well, thank you very much for the food!
I had all of it!
It was delicious!
We're going to win today, right?
I think we can win.
So I'd like to go to the race predictions.
I'd like to take a look around the boat race track a little more before I move on.
Okay.
Okay, let's go.
Well, here we are at our reserved seats on the 4th floor.
Beautiful!
It looks like it was recently renovated.
It's really beautiful.
Also, this is awesome!
This is awesome!
You can open and charge your smartphone.
It's perfect.
It's a really comfortable place.
It's really...
It's like our own private space to watch the race.
It's so cozy.
It's so cozy that one day I'm thinking
I'm thinking that maybe one day I'll come here privately and finish it like this.
It's the best seat in the house!
Oh, wait!
Oh, my gosh!
There it is! It's out!
It's out! Yes, yes!
What is this?
Does this mean I can experience boat racing in VR?
Yes, and it's a real boat.
I didn't do it.
No, I haven't.
I want to do it.
Of course I want to do it!
I'm getting gassy.
I really want to do it!
I want to do it.
I really want to do it.
I wanna do it!
Oh, yeah!
I'll take first place! Absolutely.
Absolutely?
I'll do it! I'm definitely going home in first place!
Is this a match?
This is the match.
Oh, and what?
We'll play against the other queens.
Online?
Yes! Online!
Let's go predict the race!
Yes!
Emi!
Emi-chan!
That's what I'm talking about!
In the spirit of self-portrait dedication...
pupil's guess, Emi-chan!
Emi-chan!
The girl who posed the same way!
Now for the prediction part!
Today is the 6th day of the Japan Future Project Competition in Miwa Lake!
It's the last day!
The last day!
I'm going to participate in a total of 3 races today.
On the last day, there is a championship race.
I'm talking about the 3 races from race 7 to race 9.
Today is a promotional video, so
We are introducing a special rule, the point system!
A point system!
It's the first time!
Each person has 15,000 points.
We will multiply the points by the points.
If either of the two winners has more than 100% of the total points after the end of the tournament
we will give away a prize!
One of them?
Yes!
And if either of the two of you get over 200% of the points...
You'll receive a luxurious meal ticket!
They're giving something away!
That's great!
As long as it doesn't go negative.
It's either one or the other!
It's one or the other!
It's a team game today!
Let's go for it!
Let's go!
I can do it!
Now let's get to the predictions!
I've got some idea of what to expect.
How to buy...
I don't know.
By the way, these are Boat Race Beako's characters
Mina and Venus.
Oh, my! What's that?
They are two little girls!
It's so heavy!
And I can ride it here.
I can ride here!
I can get on here!
We can ride here. Isn't this crazy?
I thought it was a hat, but it's a boat.
I can drive this thing.
Isn't this awesome? It's so cute.
So tell me about it.
Come on, let's do this together.
But listen to me.
How many times did race 7 go?
The favorite got 19.9.
That's a lot of money.
The favorite is usually in the single digits.
Nine, eight...
That's right.
The favorite is five times the price of the favorite.
I've never done that before.
As far as the boat racing club is concerned...
As you like.
I'm going to choose No. 5, Ishimoto, who's the same age as me.
I think I'll pick him.
Mr. Takahashi.
There's no Mr. Takahashi here.
You don't have a Mr. Takahashi?
Mr. Takahashi taught me a lot.
Every time I'm training to be a secretary...
They need me to teach them.
How many are you going to put on?
As many as you want.
You can use 5,000 points per race.
I don't know where they come from.
I'm losing every time.
Minus.
I'm gonna put you on the edge of your seat.
That's right.
Shimada, the sixth driver in race seven.
His motor number is 57.
Boat races.
He's a Miwako.
The top of the motor's row
There is a strong motor
The number one.
No. 57.
Bira-chan motor.
It's called "Bira-chan motor.
At Miwako's...
Today is a rare day.
It's a rare day to aim for a hole.
I'm going to make a six right now, I'm sure of it.
Leave it to me.
Braille's on.
The first hand is bright red.
That's the strongest one.
I knew it.
I like the straight line of move 6.
It's a good stretch.
But not today.
Already there.
You say he's stretching.
The five races today just now...
43,430 yen.
That's pretty bad, isn't it?
Isn't it too hard to predict?
Isn't this really difficult? This Japanese!
Reporter's forecast
Reporter's Forecast
One, two, three, four, five, two, three, four, five.
I don't understand.
He's coming off erotically.
Usually.
Rina-chan water.
I might believe Rina-chan water.
I want to believe in Rina-chan Water.
I think she'll come in third.
Shall we go then?
Okay, then.
Here's one from Maika.
Well...
It's really good.
First of all, this is a simple three-piece.
And this is...
One, three, five, one, five, three.
Fifteen hundred yen.
If this comes in, we're too rich.
Come on. Come on.
One, two, three, six.
Six.
Rina-chan's got water, so I'll put it in.
That's good.
Maybe this is the place.
Yes, yes, yes...
Hitomu?
I'm here.
Bang.
This is Mirinya box
This time, I'm going to use this Rina-chan water.
I'm
6 at all to believe
That's a crazy way to buy.
Anyway, I'm hoping that 6 is in the third place.
Rina-chan water
It's okay, but the other players
but the others are strong.
And the flying one is already in front of the other.
I don't think she'll go that hard.
I think she'll finish third.
Good luck!
Rina-chan Water
And so the races begin.
Seven races.
Even me, like Hitomi.
Wow! I don't think I can do something like that.
No one else can do it.
I'm the only one who's ever done it.
Me and the director.
Everybody just stay calm.
I can do it. I'm fine.
I'm just crazy.
It's nice to know that every time you're a boat racer.
It's nice to have their support.
I'm definitely happy.
I'd be happy if Hitomi corrected me.
If it were me, I'd be super happy.
Can you do your best?
I can do it.
That's a lot of work.
Yes! Go!
All right, all right, all right, all right.
Go, go, go, go!
GO!
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
One is coming. Oh, wait, five is coming.
Go, Ishimoto! Ishimoto!
Oh, wait.
2? Oh, 2 is coming.
Oh, 6? 6?
Come on! Wait!
30! 30! 30! 30! 30! 30!
30! 30! 30! 30! 30!
Hey, Tober.
Oh, shit.
Oh!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Three is coming!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no! That's scary.
Wow, two?
Go, go, go, go, go!
One, two...
Stiff!
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you.
Oh, no!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no.
oh no!
righteous oficial
wow!!!!
shii
totally nekkles
Saku aby
fast katan
I should have made it 2.
here
Wow!
Oh!
Wait!
We're going to the Chauffeured Mini Team!
Oh, my gosh!
First place wins!
It's gone!
It's a winner! It's a winner!
But wait a minute! Big deal! I only paid 100 yen!
How about this? Will God show up?
Oh!
Wow!
Win.
Thank you. We won.
Amazing.
Thank you very much.
You were so loud.
You were spinning around.
It's all gone.
What's the 8th place now?
This is the 8th place exhibit.
The next one's pretty ticklish at this point.
Really?
Popular? Most popular.
6.3. - What?
I'll take 2.
That's only 600 points.
Here we go.
There you go.
Number one by far.
There's nothing on 4.
That's a last-minute guess.
One, two, three, four, front.
One?
I'll write one.
That's it.
One, two, three, four.
But if you do 1, 2, 3, 4, front
In this race.
1, 2, 3, 4, front.
You have to break through all of them.
It doesn't make sense.
It doesn't, it doesn't, it doesn't mean that I
Well, then, I'm in.
Shall I announce it?
Yes, sir.
Race eight.
Dan!
Yes, sir.
Boxes one, two and four.
Ooh!
Six hundred points.
Yeah, 600 points.
One, five, three.
Two horses
Oh, that's nice.
Two was so cool.
That was a cool turn.
The turn was really good.
He was so good.
I wish you the best.
Work hard?
I was also a little concerned about the second one.
I was also a little concerned about 2.
2, not at all.
There's a lot of great front.
Five.
Like earlier.
Like the 6-minute hand in race 7 just now.
I was thinking that it would be very nice
I'd like it very much.
Basically, I'm aiming for the hole again today.
I have 200 points left over.
I'll give you 3, 1, 2 as an extra.
But it's kind of popular, isn't it?
This one.
The one I just popped was surprisingly popular.
Maybe...
Maybe that one will be born.
It's so popular.
But let's go with this.
Go, go, go!
There's a lot of shouting.
There are others like me.
All right, eight races.
Go!
It's good.
Nakajima's off to a good start.
Two's in trouble.
Good luck, 2.
Uh, 2.
Whoa!
Go, go, go, go!
Oh, wait!
Go!
Wait, I got it, I got it!
세번して大 gutes
Wan isa
Circle isa
drowning
Green at the end just now
cheer
stomach stutter
grass
Four, four, four, four!
I don't know, I don't know!
Vita vita! Vita vita! Vitter vitter!
Oh, no! Oh, no! Oh, no! Vita-va-vita, second place!
Second place, bitter bitter!
Hold on, hold on, hold on!
Second place!
Come on, guys!
Oh, no! Oh, my God!
Four!
Where's Blue? Blue! Blue!
Good luck with second place!
One stroke at a time.
One stroke.
How's it going?
What's red?
Three.
No, no, no.
Blue!
Blue! Blue! Blue! Blue! Blue! Blue! Blue! Blue!
Blue! Blue! Blue! Blue! Blue! Blue! Blue! Blue! Blue!
Stop!
Blue! Blue! Blue! Blue! Blue!
Blue! Blue! Blue!
Go blue!
Three times!
Wow, that's frustrating.
Oh, my God, it's 123456.
Oh, wow, that's right.
Wow!
I was already having so much fun until about halfway through.
It was 123.
This isn't the most popular one, is it?
It's a big favorite. 780 yen.
It's 780 yen, so even if you're right...
That's right.
Then let's continue to watch the steeplechase exhibit.
But next time, I have something special for you.
Yes, what a steeplechase!
Three of them are from Aichi.
What does that mean?
We'll have an Aichi BOX!
Yes!
Aichi BOX!
Let's have Aichi BOX!
Oh!
346...
No, it's too much!
I wonder how much the Aichi BOX is now.
What?
Awww!
5.2 million!
I'm rooting for them!
Seriously, I'll cheer for you!
But I knew it. 1 is here.
It's 1, right?
Oh, here it comes.
Prediction
21346.
What, 1?
I don't know.
It's going to be like this.
I'm thinking.
Here comes this... here comes this...
One? From here?
Two.
Two is bad.
Shall we announce?
Yes, sir.
It's done.
Quick race.
This way.
First of all, Aichi BOX is the best.
If the Aichi BOX comes, it's the best!
I can already buy one for me in the green car!
I wish Aichi BOX would come!
And then, well, 123124...
Two.
So when the first one goes, the second one goes.
Yes, yes, yes, yes...
That's right.
He'll even predict how it's going to turn out.
He's here.
Let's see what happens.
Like this, like this, like this.
I'm gonna go like this.
Okay.
So, if you come to this one, too...
Twenty-three, twelve.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And 3, you're in.
This is so good!
If only 3 would say something like this to 1.
Perfect.
Okay, here we go.
This one, 13443, is just a little bit more interesting.
I took it off because 2 is too popular this time.
I removed it.
And this fluorescent green.
I was really bothered by the fluorescent green
I couldn't help but notice it.
We will make use of it again in 136.
Yes, sir.
And finally, I had 600 points left over.
I thought, "This can be a BOX!
More BOX
It looks like it's a little too much, so...
I'm going to make the most of this.
If it comes, it's bad.
This one's even worse!
This is a hundred times worse.
I wish they'd come this way.
It's so bad.
I'm really looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to this race.
Callan's here.
I've got Curran.
Okay, here we go.
Quick race.
Let's go
Whoo-hoo!
How's it going?
But wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
What, one? Oh, one.
Whoo-hoo!
I'm in! I'm in!
Whoo-hoo! Go, go, go! Wait, wait! I don't know, I don't know!
Wait! I don't know! I don't know! We don't know what's going on yet!
But six! Six?
Wait! What if this one here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here! What about this one here!
Yeah! One go, one go, one go, one go!
Wait, there's a 6 coming in! Six coming in at 300!
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
666! Tilt free!
Wait! What are you doing? What are you doing?
Please, please, please, please, please! Please, please, please, please!
I got it, I got it, I got it!
Fluorescent green!
Oh, my God!
Don't let me see it!
Don't let me see it! Fluorescent green!
Please, please, please, please!
I'm serious, I'm serious, I'm serious, I'm serious!
I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it!
I can do it, I can do it, I can do it, I can do it!
Hyogo green
yr
I can't do it!
tel
Teden
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Please, please, please.
Desire!
Please, please, please!
Please!
I'm losing it!
No.
No!
Go, go, go!
Ranking!
I'm having fun.
Here comes Atcha, here comes Atcha!
Ouch! Don't lose! Don't lose!
Rust! Oh, no!
Nobel! Nobel! Nobel!
Yes!
That's great!
Sir!
Yes!
Six in a row!
And 600 points!
Six times 3.330 points!
What?
That's amazing!
I've already got 7 new sirens!
That's great, honey!
Now we're at 19,980 points!
Oh, my God!
All of it!
Are you serious?
Beer, Coke, and a healthy Billy!
Sir, we won it all today on six.
Six.
And that's three races down!
That didn't take long.
Three races early, huh?
Well, Maika...
I lost all of them.
Hey, I haven't told you yet.
You don't look as if you lost everything.
I know, but I thought you had the best taste.
What?
The way you picked them.
I'm going to have a hard time learning the formations.
I'll come back to study the formations next time.
Okay.
Let's do the aichbox again.
No, I want to do Aichi-Box again.
Yes, and...
And this time, the director...
Plus.
13230 points.
Recovery rate...
188.29%!
Wow!
Oh my God! I haven't won in a long time!
It's a plus!
Thank you so much!
I won with the 6th hand today, so...
I'm glad I believed you.
That's great.
Thank you so much.
I have over 100% recovery rate.
I get a prize.
Well, it's too bad it didn't go over 200%.
I don't think I'm going to get the meal ticket this time.
That's too close.
Only 12% to go.
That's almost it.
About half.
But it means we get a present.
Oh, my God.
Can I take your hand?
Seriously, what?
I don't know.
Please do it with something real.
I'm serious.
I want you to do it with something proper.
Hitomi's favorite.
Hitomi's favorite autographed item.
Oh?
From India.
Amazing!
Autographed goods
What? What?
Signature items
Huh? What?
Seriously?
What? What?
What?
Seriously?
Thank you so much.
Oh, my God.
Wait a minute.
What if you hadn't won?
What would you have done?
I'm so proud.
Oh, my God!
Thank you so much.
I will continue to support Endo Evish
I will continue to support Endo Evish as much as I can.
Thank you very much.
Oh!
If Sig makes it to the top three.
I can rate at least two for dinner today!
Oh!
Third place?
That's a top three, right?
Very funny.
A big beef.
Oh!
Speaking of sigs...
Big-boned bulls?
We'll finish first and second.
Yes, yes, of course.
Thank you very much.
Ah!
Who's there!
Who's there! He bumped into me!
You've got to be kidding me!
I'm serious!
I'll never forgive you!
Who hit me!
He hit me!
I'll never forgive you!
Last but not least, I'd like to remind everyone that the G2 8th Ladies All Star will be held from Tuesday, February 20th to Sunday, February 25th at Boat Race Miwako.
This is my favorite Ladies' race, where all professional racers are women!
The Ladies All Star is one of the four major women's races, and it is held only for female racers selected by fan votes and by a committee.
There's a fan vote and all that. Oh, yeah. Here are the top six.
They're all very famous. I know them all. Do you know them already?
Miho Moriya has a child, and I've been supporting her since before she went on maternity leave.
The first 12 races on the first day will be run by these six riders, and they're all very strong.
It's easy to see how the race will unfold... and the in-race margin of victory tends to be about 5 percent lower for the women.
It's hard for the first white boat to escape. Seriously, it's a very fun and interesting race exhibition, so I hope you'll watch it with me.
And one more thing I want to let you know is that if you buy a boat ticket at Boat Race Miho by phone, you usually get one oumi for every 100 yen you spend.
You can get a cash bag and various other privileges depending on the points you earn.
There is no membership fee and no annual fee, and the six ladies' all-star jumpers we signed this time are the prizes of the Oumi Point Club.
And now, six of our signed Ladies All-Star jumpers will be featured as giveaways in the Oumi Points Club! I wrote that!
Please check the Oumi Point Club website in the overview section for more details.
That's it for the first half of the video.
Please look forward to the second half of the video! Thank you very much for watching!
See you soon!